prmac.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to prMac, a service brought to you by GeekSuit LLC. This policy concerns the use of the prMac website at https://prmac.com. We respect and take care to maintain your privacy. prMac does not share or sell information with any other organization for commercial purposes, except to provide the service you've requested of us.

You must be 18 years of age or older to use prMac service and this privacy policy makes no provision for use of the site by those younger.

We limit access to personal information about you only to those we believe reasonably need access to that information for the purpose of the services prMac offers.

Registration information includes your email address, real, legal name, company name or affiliation, company or personal address, company or home phone number, and website address. You can change your prMac account information at any time. Your account information is password-protected, and in certain areas prMac uses SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

You can request to delete your prMac account at any time. Your identification, billing and contact information will be promptly deleted after you have cancelled your account.

prMac uses the information we collect for the purpose of products and service improvement, billing, identification and authentication, contact, research, and statistics. prMac automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request. We may send you limited communications relating to prMac, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your account.

If you desire to use an Extended option to send your Press Releases, we require your billing address and credit card information. When you register with us, your personal information and other data will be stored and processed in the United States.

Given the nature of the internet, if you post personal information in the public portions of prMac, you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties in return.

We are required to reveal personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities such as suspected fraud, threats to the safety of any person, violations of our terms of service, spamming, or as may otherwise be required by law.

prMac may be required to disclose personal information under special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal processes, or to establish or exercise our own legal rights, and to defend against legal claims.

prMac displays targeted advertisements based on personal information that is exhibited in members's profiles.

Unless you otherwise notify GeekSuit LLC in writing, you hereby grant prMac and GeekSuit LLC a limited license to prominently display your trade name, trademarks, logos, domain names and other distinctive brand features only where it regards your Press Release(s).

prMac may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

If you have questions or suggestions please contact us.
